rajb2b.com 2012-06-22

# Rajb2b.com yellow pages privacy statement

#### RAJB2B.COM YELLOW PAGES PRIVACY STATEMENT

RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your organization's information will be treated as you use our service. This policy may change from time to time as we update current services or add new services, so please check back.

**This policy will let you know:**

  * What personally identifiable information RAJB2B.COMcollects from you
  * What cookies are and how RAJB2B.COM uses them
  * How RAJB2B.COM uses your information
  * With whom does RAJB2B.COM share my information?
  * What your choices are regarding collection, use, and distribution of information
  * What is Rajb2b.com’s policy on allowing updates, corrections, or deletions
  * General information about privacy

**  
What Personally Identifiable Information RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages Collects From You  
**

RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site. Some personal and business information is gathered when you voluntarily register your business. During registration, RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages asks for contact names, titles, addresses, email addresses, industry classification and details on your company products and services. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better service we can provide. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages - you are given a User ID and are able to take full advantage of RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages many offerings. In addition to registration we may ask you for information at other times, such as in general "contact us" forms, surveys, or in customer service calls.

**What Are Cookies and How Does RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages Use Them  
**

We use a feature of your Internet Web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use these cookie files to store information as you go through the registration process, to keep track of information you have input in each step. Cookies are also used to help save and retrieve passwords used for updating your record or accessing our database.

RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve information about you from your computer.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to post your profile in RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages.

Please also note that We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**How Does RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages Use My Information?  
**

The primary goal for RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages in collecting your company information is to present your business profile to businesses interested in engaging in commercial transactions and trade. We do this by making your listing available in our web directories and by publishing a portion of your profile in our affiliate directories and partner websites.

As a registered user, you will receive membership related emails from RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages as well as special offers from RAJB2B.COM partners and affiliates. An example would be annual reminder to update your profile or an announcement about new services or special offers available to you as a member of Rajb2b.com.

**With Whom Does RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages Share My Information?  
**

RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages will not sell any of your information to third parties such as list brokers. Notwithstanding, as a registered user, you accept that your business listing will be made available to the public and RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages members through our public directory of businesses as well as in our partner directory network. On occasion, RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages may also share non-personal, summary information regarding our registrants with unrelated third parties. For example, we will share personal and/or financial information with our merchant account and banking vendors to process orders and payments and with common carriers to ship products to you. We will also publicly disclose the aggregate number of registered users of our web site to potential advertisers.

Notwithstanding the above, except as otherwise required by law or by court order, RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages will not disclose, share or sell any customer information to any other third party without your prior authorization. Unless otherwise stated, this privacy policy does not apply to information posted by users to publicly accessible portions of our websites, including but not limited to, online forums, bulletin boards, dealer listings or online auction services.

**What are My Choices Regarding Collection, Use and Distribution of My Information?  
**

In the registration process, you may opt to receive offers from our partners and affiliates. RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages and its partners will send you these direct mailings only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to register RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages business listing service.

Except as otherwise required by law or by court order, if you opt-in or subscribe to one or more of RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages' mailing lists, RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages may use your customer information to notify you by mail, telephone or email about various RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages’ advertisements and promotions. Furthermore, if you opt-in or subscribe to one or more of RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages’ mailing lists, RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages may also share customer information to RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages' affiliates and partners who may use your customer information to send you advertisements and promotions offered by such third party affiliates and partners. You may opt-out from receiving such advertisements and promotions from RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages at any time by following the instructions contained in any email solicitation or by contacting RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages at [mail@rajb2b.com](mailto:mail@rajb2b.com) 

**What Is RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages' Policy on Allowing Me to Update, Correct, or Delete My Personally Identifiable Information?  
**

You may edit your RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages Account Information and your public RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages Profile at any time. RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages moderates each listing prior to posting to our directory. RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages reserves the right to make appropriate changes to your listing in relation to typographical errors and formatting of your listing. Your RAJB2B.COM Yellow Pages account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in your account not being able to access the database.

Your account can be deactivated from the web site by submitting a request to [mail@rajb2b.com](mailto:mail@rajb2b.com)  Your record will remain within our archive records.

**What Else Should I Know About My Privacy?  
**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - specifically in our business listings - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post your information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Additional Information  
**

If you have a question that was not addressed in this privacy policy you may contact us at [mail@rajb2b.com](mailto:mail@rajb2b.com)
